<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ayini</string>

    <string name="phImpt">The relative acidity or alkalinity of soil is indicated by its pH.
        The pH scale runs from 0 to 14. Any pH reading below 7 is acidic and any pH above 7 is alkaline. A pH of 7 indicates a neutral soil.
        The pH is important because it influences the availability of essential nutrients.
        Most horticultural crops will grow satisfactorily in soils having a pH between 6 (slightly acid) and 7.5 (slightly alkaline).</string>
    <string name="NitImpt">Nitrogen (N) is one of the most important nutrients required for crop production.
        Application of fertilizer N results in increased growth and higher biomass yields.
        It directly influences the amino acid composition of protein and thereby nutritional quality of the economic produce.
        Effects of N fertilization are different in different crops.</string>
    <string name="PhoImpt">Phosphorus plays a major role in the growth of new tissue and division of cells.
        Plants perform complex energy transmissions, a function that requires phosphorus.</string>
    <string name="PotImpt">In Photosynthesis, potassium regulates the opening and closing of stomata, and therefore regulates CO2 uptake.
        Potassium triggers activation of enzymes and is essential for production of Adenosine Triphosphate (ATP).
        ATP is an important energy source for many chemical processes taking place in plant issues.</string>
    <string name="CalImpt">Calcium plays a very important role in plant growth and nutrition, as well as in cell wall deposition.
        The primary roles of calcium:
        As a soil amendment, calcium helps to maintain chemical balance in the soil, reduces soil salinity, and improves water penetration.</string>
    <string name="MagImpt">Magnesium is a macronutrient that is necessary to both plant growth and health.
        It is involved in several different processes,
        including photosynthesis, which nearly all living organisms are dependent on.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="moisture">Moisture</string>
    <string name="acidity_p_h">Acidity (p.H)</string>
    <string name="fertility">Humidity</string>
    <string name="additional_monitoring">Additional Monitoring</string>
</resources>
